Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You have to stop the bleeding.
Palestine Red Crescent
This is the Palestine Red Crescent.
How can I help you?
An ambulance is on its way.
The nearest ambulance is on its way.
I can't hear you.
All right.
At the end of Nazareth Street.
there's a roundabout.
Then go straight ahead.
Straight on.
Don't worry. I can see you.
Keep going straight.
You're in red on my map.
Did you get that done for me?
Ah. the report.
Perfect. thank you.
Are you all right?
Everything OK?
- Rana.
- Nisreen.
You're still here?
Weren't you going home this morning?
I still have one more thing to finish.
I'm exhausted.
I can't wait to get home.
Rock. paper. scissors.
6-3. I'm kicking your ass.
Hold on a second.
I have an emergency call.
Red Crescent emergency room. Ramallah.
This is Omar. how can I help you?
Emergency calls from Gaza have been
transferred here since the bombing.
Hold on... Where?
Gaza?
But you're calling me from Germany?
All right.
Send me your brother's number
and the location of his car.
OK. thanks.
Mahdi?
Yes. Omar.
I might need an ambulance
in the north of Gaza.
In the north?
At a gas station.
Let me check. stay with me.
At the Fares gas station.
What's it all about?
Bashar Hamada. his wife and children
were evacuating Tel Al-Hawa by car.
They were hit 400 meters
from their home.
near the Fares service station at 1 p.m.
- At 1 p.m.?
- Yes.
It's 2:35 p.m.
That was an hour and a half ago.
Yes. that's right.
Are there any survivors?
I spoke to his brother in Germany.
He doesn't know
if they're still hidden in the car.
or if they managed to escape on foot.
He's panicked. It's not clear.
It's in a restricted zone.
The army sealed it off this morning.
Call this number. he'll answer.
- I have their phone number.
- Call them.
I'll call. Stay with me.
It's ringing.
Hello?
Hello.
They're shooting at us!
The tank is next to me!
Are you hiding?
Yes. in the car.
The tank is next to us.
Are you inside the car?
Omar?
Is she still on the line?
Omar. you need to speak with Rana.
She's your supervisor.
Omar was talking to a girl in Gaza.
There was a shooting.
Omar?
Are you all right?
Do you need counselling?
Shall I call Nisreen?
No.
They killed her.
What's her name?
She didn't have time to say.
Omar.
Hello. Omar.
How do you feel?
See these?
We stick them to our desk.
when we don't have a name or photo
of those who died during a call.
When we receive their photos.
we hang them over there.
As a tribute
and out of respect for them.
And it allows you...
to move forward
and be able to help others.
Thank you.
Omar.
If you need to talk. I'm here.
My door is always open to you.
You can let off steam.
OK? Don't be shy.
I have to go back.
I'm going home.
Do you need anything?
It's fine. go home and rest.
A 6-year-old girl is alive in the car.
Call her.
Rana. come!
What is it. Omar?
The uncle says that a 6-year-old girl
is still hidden in the car.
Fine. call her.
Omar?
Go ahead. you're trained for this.
Call her.
I'm going home.
Hello. Uncle?
Hello.
Stay with me!
Listen. sweetheart. concentrate.
Tell me what happened.
Hello?
There's no time!
What? Are you hiding?
Quick!
What's your name?
There's no one with me.
I can't hear your name.
I'm Omar. what's your name?
My name is Hanood.
What's your name?
Hanood.
Hanood?
- And your sister's name?
- Come get me.
- Where's your sister?
- Come get me!
- I will. but where's your sister?
- I don't have one.
- Mahdi?
- Yes. Omar.
A 6-year-old girl
is still hidden in the car.
A 6-year-old girl in the car?
And the others?
The others. I don't know.
She says she's alone.
She's on the line with me.
- Who's on the line with you?
- The girl.
Is she a member of the Hamada family?
Ask her.
Hanood?
What's your full name?
Hind Rajab Hamada.
Hind Rajab Hamada?
OK.
Rana.
Hide under the seats.
Don't let anyone see you.
Stay with her.
OK?
Yes.
Where are your parents?
They're not here.
Hold on. OK?
I'll call you back right now.
No. Come get me.
They're shooting.
Have you made any progress?
I'm waiting to find out
which of our rescuers are available.
She doesn't have time.
Call them back quickly. please.
There's no point in calling back.
They need to collect the information
and get back to me.
Hanood?
Don't hang up. I'll be right back.
OK.
We've only got one team left
in the north.
Call them directly.
Go back to talking to the little one
and let me do my job.
Call Zaïno directly.
Ibrahim is in charge
of rescuers in Gaza.
He decides whether we call them or not.
They're shooting at her.
They will kill her.
just like the other girl.
Ask Rana to come and get Omar.
Mahdi.
They're shooting at her.
Here he is.
Hello. Ibrahim?
Go on.
One moment.
I'll take note. Just a second.
Rescuers. Youssef Zaïno.
Youssef Zaïno. my buddy.
Driver.
Madhoun. who else?
Ahmed Madhoun.
Type of ambulance.
Savana.
3...
1-0-7...
4...
5-5.
- OK.
- Call Zaïno.
OK. thanks.
I'm starting the coordination.
The coordination?
She doesn't have time!
I'll call Zaïno
to see if there's another solution.
There isn't.
Why would you call Zaïno?
Why would you talk to him?
Are you his supervisor?
No. but I want to save the girl!
It's not your job to save the girl.
It's mine.
Your job is to maintain contact with her
while we coordinate to save her.
And from now on.
wear your Red Crescent jacket!
What's going on here?
I'm trying to start the coordination
but Omar won't take it easy.
The coordination?
Let's hope this time
it won't take nine hours.
Come on. Omar.
Let's hope so.
Hind?
Who is it?
My name is Rana.
And you're Hanood. right?
Yes.
Zaïno isn't answering.
Omar. I told you.
it's my job to call Zaïno.
I'm just telling you
he has no reception.
The army is jamming
all the phone lines in Gaza.
It's Zaïno.
Hello. Zaïno?
What's up. buddy?
Where are you?
At the Baptist Hospital?
Give it to me. Omar.
Are you at the Baptist Hospital?
I'll put you on
to the head of coordination.
chief negotiator. the martyr. the hero.
Mahdi Aljamal. Here you go.
Hello. Zaïno. Is everything OK?
Are you with Madhoun
at the Baptist Hospital?
Not at the Saint-Porphyrius Church?
Fine.
You're 8 minutes from your mission.
Please. Zaïno.
just listen to my instructions.
OK?
Yes. my friend.
We've got an impossible mission for you.
Hello. Ibrahim.
I've started the coordination.
Don't worry. I'm not going to sacrifice
our last team in the north.
I'm going to guarantee them
a safe route
before sending them on their mission.
Hello. Hind.
We've been talking to Hind
for 8 minutes.
The ambulance
could have picked her up by now.
Hind?
My darling. Hanood.
Mommy?
Sweetheart. I'm staying with you
until someone comes to get you.
- All right?
- All right.
Where are you hiding now?
Have you found a safe spot?
I'm in the car.
You're inside the car.
not outside. right?
Yes.
Is anyone near you?
Who can see you. or can speak to you?
No.
Well. my darling.
Who were you with?
My whole family.
Who in your family?
How many of them are there?
Do you know their names?
Can you tell me their names?
No.
Were Mommy and Daddy with you?
The army shot at you. right. darling?
Hanood. sweetheart?
Come!
Okay. sweetie. calm down.
Listen to me.
I'd like...
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
OK?
- Hanood?
- Yes.
OK. listen to me.
When you were shot at.
who was with you?
- Your dad...
- My whole family.
Your mother and father were with you
inside the car?
Or just outside the car?
No.
My mom isn't dead.
How many siblings do you have?
I just have one brother.
How old is he?
Three years old.
My brother is at home with my mom.
- What's your brother's name?
- Iyad.
- Zyad?
- Yes.
And your sister's name?
I don't have a sister.
Who was in the car with you?
Nobody.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
There isn't anyone with you?
Are you alone in the car right now?
Yes.
I'm here with no family. no mother.
no father.
no brother.
There's only us and Sarah.
Sarah? Where is Sarah?
Sarah is next to me.
Is Sarah with you now?
Sarah...
Yes.
Hanood. sweetheart.
Sarah. she's the one
who spoke with Uncle? Right?
- The one who was talking to you before?
- No.
Can Sarah talk?
Yes.
Is Sarah hurt?
Does she have blood on her?
She has blood on her. yes.
Is she next to you
or in the front seat?
What?
Is Sarah next to you?
Yes.
Sarah can talk? Talk to her.
But Sarah is sleeping.
Is Sarah sleeping?
Yes.
Someone's calling me.
Hanood?
It's her uncle. He's calling me.
Mahdi.
Don't ask me if I've made any progress.
I'll let you know
as soon as I get an answer.
Hello.
Go back to your office.
I haven't been home
or seen my children in two months.
And you can't put up with this
for 24 hours?
We are sending an ambulance.
Yes. we're sending an ambulance.
I wanted to ask you:
Who's Sarah?
Do you have a photo of her?
All right.
I will stay in touch.
Thank you.
What did he say?
Someone in the family had Layan and Hind
on the phone before me.
- Only Layan and Hind were alive.
- Who's Layan?
The girl I spoke to on the phone first.
She's Hind's cousin.
In the car there's her aunt.
uncle and four cousins.
I'm alone.
I'm on my own.
You're...
So you're the only one who's awake?
No one else is moving. covered in blood?
Yes. they're covered in blood.
Please. don't leave me.
So if I'm not mistaken. in the car.
there's your uncle. your aunt.
and their four children.
and they're asleep.
So they're with you?
Yes.
Then let them sleep.
At home. when the others are asleep.
we shouldn't make any noise. right?
Let them rest a while.
The trip must have tired them out.
The girl is in there with six corpses.
Call the Red Cross.
Mahdi. she thinks they're asleep.
It's true that they were hit by gunfire.
it's true that they are bleeding.
But right now. they need to sleep.
You can say they're sleeping. right?
I said they are dead!
They're all dead.
What. darling?
They're dead.
They're dead?
Yes.
They're dead.
There are only dead bodies.
My whole family.
They're all dead!
Send the rescuers!
What's your problem?
They just need 8 minutes
to save the girl!
Without coordination. those 8 minutes
can cost them their lives. Omar.
Mahdi. those guys are skilled.
and have saved a lot of lives.
Please call them.
it's not their first rescue.
Omar. you're going
to finish me off today.
See all these people?
Take a good look at them.
He had two children.
He had four.
Three girls and one boy.
She'd just gotten engaged.
I knew them well.
They had families. children.
stories. dreams and ambitions.
Like you and me.
Bombed. We've lost them all.
They were our best rescuers.
I promised myself I'd stop.
if one more photo
was added to this wall.
We need to guarantee a safe route.
approved by the army.
so they can carry out the rescue.
How can you coordinate with the army
who killed them and all those people?
Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding?
I never coordinate directly
with the army.
We go through the Red Cross
or the West Bank Ministry of Health.
How did they hit you?
They shot at us.
They shot at you from a house?
Or were they on foot?
Or from an airplane?
No. from a tank.
They fired from a tank?
Yes.
What do you like?
How were you like. at school?
A school kid.
- Do you have any water in the car?
- No.
- Any food?
Nothing at all.
Talk to her about something else.
What grade are you in?
I'm in the butterfly class.
- What?
- The butterfly class.
Are you in pre-school?
I can't hear you.
- I said. are you in pre-school?
- Yes.
What's the name of your school?
A Happy Childhood.
- A Happy Childhood?
- Yes.
Are you very good at school?
What color do you like?
I don't like anything.
What color?
I don't like anything!
- What color clothes are you wearing?
- I can't hear you.
I can hear you. Talk to me.
I'll talk to her.
She's more comfortable with me.
Wait. Hanood.
I'm all alone.
I know you're alone.
But God is with us.
Stay with me.
I'm with you.
I'm with you. sweetheart.
Until someone comes to get you.
I won't leave you on your own.
What?
When they come. will you hang up?
No. I'm staying with you.
I'm with you.
If someone from the army arrives.
don't hang up. stay on the phone.
I'm with you.
OK.
Hanood. darling?
Let's talk.
but I'm going to ask you
to look out the window.
If you can. of course.
But if you prefer to see nothing
and hide. do that.
Can you see from the window
what's going on out there?
What. darling?
They're shooting at me!
They're shooting at her.
Tell me. what do you like?
Please. come get me!
I'm scared.
Repeat: Dear God...
Protect us...
Do you want us to recite the Koran?
OK.
Let's pray. OK?
Yes.
In the name of God.
the Beneficent. the Merciful.
All praise is due to God.
the Lord of the Worlds.
The Beneficent. the Merciful.
Master of the Day of Judgment.
Thee do we serve
and Thee do we beseech for help.
Keep us on the right path.
The path of those upon whom
Thou hast bestowed favors.
Not of those upon whom
Thy wrath is brought down.
nor of those who go astray.
Amen.
God has spoken the truth.
Well done. you recite well.
Come get me. please.
Don't cry. do you want more prayers?
The tank is next to me.
Where's the tank?
Next to me.
Is the tank next to you?
Is it moving or did it stop?
Did anyone get out?
No. it's moving forward.
- It's moving?
- Yes.
Is it coming from the side.
from behind or from the front?
From the front.
It's coming from the front of the car?
Yes.
- Is it close?
- Very. very close.
- Is it coming towards you?
- The tanks are here!
Please. come.
The tanks are coming!
The line is bad. I'll call her back.
Very. very close.
- Is it coming towards you?
- The tanks are here!
Please. come.
The tanks are coming!
- Is it coming towards you?
- The tanks are here!
Please. come.
The tanks are coming!
What happened?
I'm trying to call her back.
We've been on the phone with her
for an hour.
We only needed 8 minutes to save her.
Excuse me.
A man called Mohamed Hamada
keeps calling.
He wants to speak to the head
of coordination. On line two.
It's her uncle. Talk to him.
You can't smoke in here.
I know it's long.
Because our ambulance
is 8 minutes away from the girl.
But to send it.
we have to call the Red Cross.
Not in Geneva.
They have an office in Jerusalem.
Then. they call COGAT.
COGAT?
It's a unit
of the Israeli Ministry of Defense
that coordinates activities
in the occupied territories.
No. it's not the soldiers on the ground.
This is another intermediary.
The soldiers on the ground
send us a secure route
so that our ambulance can move
without being targeted.
But they don't send us
the route directly.
It goes through COGAT.
then to the Red Cross.
The Red Cross sends us the route.
But receiving the route
doesn't mean we have the green light.
The green light to deploy the ambulances
is another step from A to Z.
I have to follow this procedure
to the letter.
because if we don't.
they could shoot at our ambulances.
and say it's our fault.
I know.
I know. everywhere else.
they send an ambulance immediately.
The only way is to jump
from building to building.
You stick to the walls.
Yes. like Spiderman.
It's 40 minutes away. maximum an hour.
You can do it. Madhoun.
Madhoun. you're not going anywhere
until I tell you!
- What are you doing?
- And you?
What are you doing?
The guys can save a lot of lives.
Why are you acting like this?
It's the right thing to do.
What are you talking about?
They'll save her. they're real heroes.
Not like you.
a coward hiding behind your desk!
I'm a coward?
Fuck your green light!
Fuck your coordination!
People die every second!
- Every second!
- Do you want them to die too?
It's because of people like you
that we're occupied!
No. no.
She's not dead.
Nisreen. please come.
Take a deep breath.
I couldn't save her.
I understand.
Drink some water.
Drink.
Take a deep breath.
Look at me.
You did the best you could.
Take a deep breath.
Let's go outside and catch our breath.
Come on. darling.
- Cigarette?
- You can't smoke in here.
Hello.
A woman
who was about to give birth called.
She was alone and under siege
with her 10-year-old sister.
We called an obstetrician
who helped us over the phone.
He guided the little sister
on what she had to do.
Step by step.
I was on the phone.
It took five hours.
She gave birth.
It was magical to hear the baby's cry.
I felt so useful.
I can't describe the feeling.
I did my makeup. Full makeup!
I don't know what came over me.
Can you send me her mother's number?
Hello.
Are you Hind's mother?
I'm calling from the Red Crescent.
May I ask a question?
Please listen. don't shout at me.
I just have one question.
When was the last time
you spoke to Hind?
Right now. before I called you?
All right!
The child is alive! Come with me.
She's alive!
Hanood!
Don't hang up. Stay on the line.
Here. take that.
Did she say "sorry"?
It will be dark soon.
What?
It will be dark soon. I'm scared.
Can you speak a little louder?
Pass her to me. Mahdi.
She says. "sorry"!
Shut the fuck up!
I won't accept this!
Omar.
What's going on?
The Red Cross doesn't want
to coordinate anymore.
So what? It's not a big deal.
Call our Ministry of Health.
You still have options.
Hello. Doctor.
Mahdi speaking. from the Red Crescent.
Please may I ask you
to coordinate with the army.
and send an ambulance?
The little girl is trapped in a car
with the corpses of her family.
Surrounded by tanks and bombing.
The place is under siege.
We need coordination.
Thank you. Doctor.
I'll wait to hear from you.
I'll send you the details.
Our rescuers are ready.
What's happening?
We're on again.
- What?
- Back to square one.
You hear?
Yes. darling.
They're shooting at me.
I hear that they're shooting at you.
Come get me.
- Please. come!
- Sweetheart...
I'm all on my own!
I swear.
I wish I could come.
Ask your husband to bring you here.
Ask my husband to take me to you?
Yes.
My husband is at work.
He can't take me.
Call him.
You want me to call him?
Yes.
Ok. I'll call him.
Still nothing?
We're talking
to the Ministry of Health.
- And?
- We're waiting.
My husband is far away.
We won't be able to come straight away.
We live very far away.
- What time is it?
- What?
What time is it?
I'm afraid of the dark.
You said it's getting dark. right?
But there's still some light left.
We still have some time.
I have already contacted several people.
I even contacted the ambassador.
I need your help.
I need an influential contact.
I know that the offices are closed.
I need a personal contact.
I understand ma'am.
I swear I do. but...
I really understand.
Very well. ma'am.
My colleague is trying to reassure her.
It's Hind's mother.
Talk to her. I can't take it anymore.
Is your son next to you?
Thank goodness for that!
We hope to bring Hind back to you.
May you be together again.
Please. I'm scared. Please come.
It's dark. Come!
Calm down.
You're stressing her out.
Take me away!
We'll come. sweetie. but it won't be me.
Come!
If only I could come...
I don't have that power.
But like I said.
we're organizing the coordination.
I hope it works out.
What?
What is coordination?
Explain it to her
as if it were a family.
Here. at the Red Crescent.
me. my brothers and sisters
we have a father. OK?
And the soldiers in the tanks
also have a father. OK?
Our father has to talk to their father
so we can send our brother to save you
and his sons don't shoot at him.
But now they're shooting.
Yes. I can hear that they're shooting.
Call someone to pick me up.
Call my uncles and... Call them...
and tell them to come get me.
Who?
One moment. please.
Leila needs to get the recordings.
We'll post them on social media.
and send them to the press.
Yes. sure.
Come and take a breather.
Leila. hurry. I have to call her back.
Can I have another headset?
- The headset works fine.
- No. it doesn't.
It's because she is far from the phone.
I want to talk to her.
Nisreen. let me talk to her.
- Let me talk to her!
- You'll break the earpiece!
- Give it to me!
- Rana. calm down.
Leave me alone. Nisreen.
Please!
You're going to stress the kid out.
- The important thing is to save her.
- You must calm down.
I don't care what happens to me!
I can die!
Rana. you have to recenter yourself.
Why are you screaming?
What happened to you?
Your eye?
Hanood. sweetheart.
Oh. my darling.
Speak with me. my love. but calmly.
Because I can't hear you.
And don't hang up. Stay on the line.
OK.
- Darling.
- Yes?
I just want to ask you a question.
Does your eye hurt?
What happened?
Your voice isn't always clear.
Talk to me slowly. so I can hear you.
I can't hear your name.
My name is Omar.
Will you put it in English too?
My name is Hanood.
They're shooting.
OK. hide under the seats.
No. Come get me.
They're shooting at me.
I'm scared!
She says she's scared.
I'm hurt!
Who's hurt?
Come get me.
She said she was hurt?
Hurt?
She's bleeding!
She's hurt. do something!
Publish that she's hurt
and she's bleeding.
That's a great idea.
And don't forget to write in English.
"She's hurt."
Seriously? Check out social media.
Look at them.
Take a good look.
Children's bodies ripped apart
on the side of the road.
Do you really think
the voice of a terrified little girl
will spark their empathy?
She needs an ambulance.
The rescue team!
Omar. I beg you. We're all on edge.
Hind. sweetie?
Are you hurt?
Put her on speaker.
A doctor?
Do you want to see a doctor?
The doctor has to come.
My dear. I spoke with a doctor.
He'll come and get you.
Stay where you are. OK?
- She's hurt.
- She doesn't sound like she's wounded.
She must have blood on her.
from the bodies around her.
You know the way home?
Yes. I know where my house is.
What?
But come get me.
Don't move. darling. Stay in the car.
- It's hard to breathe.
- What. sweetheart?
I'm stuck. I can't get out.
Come get me.
They're all around you. If you go now.
we don't know what might happen.
It cut off. Get up. Omar.
Doctor. Do you have any news?
Is this the Ministry of Health?
Yes. I'm the one who called
the ambassador.
Yes. I know the protocol.
One intermediary at a time.
It was just an informal call.
The little girl is bleeding and we...
We don't really know what to do.
Do we have the green light?
Give it to me.
Doctor.
Doctor. coordination
will obviously take all night.
I've got a better idea.
Can you call the army
and tell them there's a little girl
asking for help?
All they have to do
is get her out of there.
and take some pictures
for their propaganda.
Tell them to let her live.
She knows her way home.
If I were an Israeli soldier.
I'd do that.
Where do you think we live?
Do you really think
that they haven't spotted her?
Their tanks are equipped
with infrared sensors.
A red light that detects heat sources.
Corpses don't show up.
She'll show up in red
on their detector.
They can probably hear her.
The sound is gone.
I can't hear her.
She's breathing. she can hear you.
Alright.
You know. I've been trying to call you.
With the phone.
to make sure you were OK.
but Uncle Omar beat me to it.
Uncle Omar is always
one step ahead of me.
He's always on the ball.
Did we lose her?
Wouldn't that be convenient for you.
Shut up.
You know when I have a daughter.
I'll call her Hanood.
Can you hear me?
She hears you.
Hanood. could you have muted the mic?
- What do you want?
- What are you hiding?
- Open the laptop.
- No.
- Then move over.
- I'm not moving.
It doesn't concern you.
Good evening. Doctor.
I've just received it.
Thank you very much.
Open the laptop. Move over.
Omar. enough.
- Move over!
- No.
- You're going to move.
- No chance.
- Open the laptop.
- No.
What are you hiding?
Open the laptop. please.
At last!
- Call the rescuers.
- No. The girl is not speaking.
She's alive.
She was bleeding.
and now she's silent.
She can hear us.
We keep promising that we're on our way.
She doesn't believe us anymore.
The girl is still breathing
and she's alive.
Please. talk to them!
Even if she's alive.
we need the green light.
Ah. the green light.
- Give me that.
- My phone!
Mahdi. give me my phone!
Hands off!
Give me my phone!
Did I tell you my brothers and sisters
at the Red Crescent
are coordinating?
I swear. we are doing what we can.
We need to coordinate to get there.
Rana.
Rana. honey. let me talk to her.
Let me talk to her.
Let me try. It'll be fine.
Get some rest.
Give it to me.
I know your spirit is strong.
The spirit of a warrior
who loves life.
I'm going to ask you to take a breath.
A deep breath.
Imagine...
Imagine
you're smelling a flower.
Smell the flower.
hold the air you've breathed in.
Hold the air for a moment.
Hold it for a moment.
Then imagine
blowing out a candle.
And we'll be able to...
inhale. and exhale.
Inhale.
exhale.
A long exhale.
Take a deep breath. like we said.
We smell the flower.
Then blow out the candle.
Close your eyes.
And remember the sea.
The sun shining on the sea.
Remember.
how you swam in the sea.
How you played
in the water and the sand.
All of these scenes.
Remember that.
And imagine them in front of you.
Imagine the Gaza sea.
The sand of Gaza.
The beach. soft and pleasant.
How soothing it is
when you walk barefoot on the sand.
Rana?
Yes. darling.
There she is!
Hanood. my dear.
I hear you. darling.
Yes. Hanood?
- Who are you?
- I'm Nisreen. sweetie.
I'm Rana's sister. I'm Nisreen.
What. Hanood?
Save me.
I'll stay on the line with you
until you see someone
from the Red Crescent by your side.
We're going to save you. sweetheart.
Ok. darling?
Hello. Doctor.
The girl's still on the line.
she's begging us.
Any news about the green light?
I'm so happy to finally hear your voice.
So?
Still no green light.
What are they waiting for?
What do you want me to say?
I don't make the rules.
I've told you a thousand times.
No green light. no ambulance.
Mahdi. Hind's mother is screaming
on the phone.
Will you talk to her?
We have to save her. I'm begging you.
We only needed 8 minutes to save her.
We've been talking about it for hours!
Mahdi. give me my phone.
- Leave me alone.
- I'm going to speak to them.
Mahdi. give me my phone.
I'm not coming out
until we get the green light.
Give me my phone. please.
Come on. Mahdi.
Go on then. play.
Come get me quickly.
We'll be there soon.
Save me.
Of course. my treasure.
Yes. sweetheart.
Just like I promised.
I'm dying.
My darling. you're fine.
You're alive. you're breathing
and you're talking to me.
I'm dying!
We've got the green light.
We've got the green light!
Mahdi. we've got the green light!
- Hind? Hanood?
- Yes.
We're coming to get you.
Yes. Zaïno. I got you.
OK.
The street I'm on is...
Jamal Abdel Nasser Street. Exactly.
Then turn left.
They've gone.
You'll be there in no time.
You and Madhoun will do great.
Yes. ma'am.
The ambulance is on its way
I'll put you on speaker.
Your daughter can hear you.
You can talk to her. she can hear you.
- Hanood?
- Yes.
I love you. Mommy loves you.
We all love you. sweetheart.
- Are you alright?
- Yes.
Be careful.
Yes.
Don't be scared.
be as brave as a lioness.
- OK. darling?
- Yes.
They are on their way. don't be afraid.
We are on our way. very close.
They are almost there. darling.
- OK?
- Yes.
We got cut off.
What is happening?
Mahdi. why are they stopping?
They're not moving now.
There's no network.
the connection is down.
Call back.
Try Madhoun. if Zaïno doesn't respond.
Madhoun isn't answering.
There's no network.
- Maybe he...
- No.
Zaïno. why aren't you moving?
Don't move.
Wait for my call. OK?
OK. wait for my call.
- What's going on?
- The road is blocked.
A bombed-out building has collapsed.
They must be changing route.
- They're very close.
- It doesn't look like that anymore.
The map hasn't been updated.
It's all been destroyed.
Hanood. darling?
The car will arrive soon. in ten minutes.
The road is a bit...
Hello. Doctor.
- Difficult.
- Very difficult. so...
The ambulance is stuck
at the crossroads of Dahchane Street
and Al-Seena Street.
Or what's left of it.
Our guys are...
We need to correct the route.
May God soften
the hard hearts towards you.
Yes. Doctor.
Hanood?
They won't move
without the army's approval.
Don't hang up.
I'm here.
You are my love. darling.
Zaïno?
I've got a change of route.
Yes. it's from the army.
You turn left and go five meters.
no more.
Stop after no more than five meters.
Then go left.
and you're back on the original route.
Thank God for that.
Come on...
Hanood. darling.
One minute to go.
The car is moving slowly.
Great news from Uncle Omar!
I'm on...
I'm not sure. I took a right from...
- That's the Arab League Street. right?
- Exactly.
Turn right. It's 400 or 500 meters away.
maximum.
Ma'am. they're near her.
A quarter of a mile away.
Just 400 meters. They're behind her.
I'm with you. darling.
They are on their way.
They pointed a green laser at you?
All right. that means
they've identified you.
Have you coordinated?
I'm at...
There's been coordination. ma'am.
- What?
- I'm speaking to the family.
We've coordinated. We've been working
on it for three hours. Don't worry.
- It's Fares station?
- Yes. Are you close?
I'm nearly there.
Is the little girl there?
The little girl is in a car
with bullet holes.
There's a red light in the distance.
Can you hear the ambulance sirens?
Should I go and see the little girl?
Can you see the car?
No. I can't see a thing.
Did you turn on the sirens and lights?
Not the sirens.
But I turned on the lights.
There she is!
The person you are trying to reach
is not available right now.
- We lost them.
- No.
No.
The line went dead.
Call them back. please.
Ask her if there's been any shooting.
Was there a shot fired. Hind?
Hanood. was there a shot fired?
Yes.
- Was there a shot fired or not?
- She said yes.
I think she said yes automatically.
Please check with her.
This information is really important.
My darling.
Yes.
- Was there a shot fired?
- Yes.
Hanood. darling.
it's Uncle Omar talking.
- Hanood. darling?
- Yes.
Can you concentrate a little.
like you did this afternoon?
- Yes.
- OK. let's go.
Did you hear a shot fired like before?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
Yes.
So she heard a shot?
Yes. she heard it.
Has anyone come to see her?
Can I ask you something?
Can you ask...
Can you ask Hanood
if anyone came to see her?
Did our rescuers come to see her?
- Hanood. did someone come to see you?
- No.
- Did somebody come looking for you?
The ambulance is there?
No.
Don't you have any information?
- We know that...
- They're very close.
The ambulance is very close to her.
but it looks like...
We lost contact.
Maybe they're waiting for approval
to go through. they're really close.
We can see them on the computer.
We're trying to reach them
but the line is...
Let's hope that...
She'll see them any minute.
Do you have any news. Doctor?
The little girl is waiting for them.
They're close by.
They got onto Arab League Street.
May God protect you. my darling.
Don't worry. it will be ok.
But she has to hide.
like Uncle Omar told her.
Hide between the seats
and cover your head.
She's clever.
she knows what she has to do.
I'll be waiting for you sweetie.
My love. my darling.
Mommy's love.
Then. contact with Hind was lost.
Everyday. I would go
to the Baptist hospital
to wait for my daughter.
I was convinced
that my daughter was alive.
Maybe she was with the rescuers.
maybe the army had taken her.
There were so many possibilities.
I kept saying that my daughter
was alive and well.
Hind loved the sea.
The sea was like a friend to her.
She used to say:
"I just want the war to end.
"to go to the sea and play in the sand."
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today